Shepparton, Australia

**** 0490 782 726

Profile

27 years old Italian Bartender with extraordinary customer service skills and a motivated attitude. Knowledgeable about drink combinations, free-pouring techniques, and flair bartending moves. Adept at maintaining a clean and organized bar area, practicing the Clean-As-You-Go policy.

Employment History

Lifeguard, Islamorada Dog Beach, Fano (Italy)

May 2014 — September 2016

Worked for three summer seasons (2014/15/16)

- · Utilized excellent surveillance skills.
- Remained flexible, adaptable and punctual.
- Occasionally worked as a bartender during night events.

Bartender, Circolo ARCI, Corinaldo (Italy)

September 2016 — January 2017

- Greeted guests with a friendly and helpful attitude at all times.
- Carried on friendly conversations with patrons and answered any questions or concerns to the best of my ability.
- Followed directions and took initiative when appropriate.

Fruit Picker, Australia

February 2017 — March 2024

Bartender and Barista, Garagol Beach, Fano (Italy)

May 2018 — September 2018

- Waited at tables, taking drink orders in this high-traffic bar.
- Utilized excellent public speaking skills.
- Brought forth a positive and self-motivated attitude.
- Monitored bar inventory and made notes for needed supplies when necessary.
- Provided guests with drink suggestions and knowledge about drink recipes.

Bartender, TGI Fridays, Gold Coast

October 2022 — November 2022

- Greeted customers in a friendly and professional manner
- Learned and followed all store policies and procedures, resulting in fewer mistakes and improved customer service

Education

I.I.S. Volterra-Elia, Ancona (Italy)

September 2010 — June 2016

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Degree at the Industrial Technical Institute Volterra-Elia

Links

Facebook

Instagram

LinkedIn

Personal Website (under construction)

Skills

Customer Service

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Computer Skills

Ability to Work in a Team

Analytical Thinking

Languages

Italian

English

Spanish: Castilian

Hobbies

Football, Videogames, Cocktails & Poker

European Bartender School, Milan

February 2018 — April 2018

Certificate IV in Business, Greystone College, Brisbane

August 2020 — May 2021

Start2Impact University, Italy

August 2020

Following IT courses on Web and App development, blockchain technology

More than 10 projects completed and reviewed by experts

References

References available upon request